Music
Thank you for watching!
Waiting?
We're waiting
It says here.
It's glowing red.
I didn't see it.
Well, how did it go?
You know...
It's amazing.
I've never seen it before.
Through the window sill.
With fans in the audience.
When I recorded the radio show...
I felt like I was being watched.
I was so nervous.
You're nervous today, aren't you?
I'm really nervous.
It's been a while since I've been in Sendai.
We just finished a live appearance on Date FM.
Well, we always have one of our members MCing today.
But today, it's not a member, it's a professional.
Oh my...
He was so charismatic.
He was so smooth.
He was so easy to understand.
So are we... so are we.
Uiroli?
We have to do it, you know...
Yes, well...
You're not going to answer it?
We may not be able to vlog, by the way.
No?
What is Sendai for you?
It's my hometown.
I feel most at home here.
I feel the air is the best.
I've been around.
What does Sendai mean to you?
Yes, I think so.
Sendai for me is...
Well...
The future
And tomorrow
I want to take good care of Sendai.
After all...
There is a reason why I said future.
The future
Because it is the future.
You know...
We're also rivals in Tochigi.
Are you done? No, I'm not.
You're not? No, I'm not.
I'm here for the beef tongue.
Beef tongue just arrived.
Here, put the soup on the right.
Thank you very much.
Oh, man.
It's good.
Rice and soup.
It smells so good.
Rice
Hale Soup
I did something wrong.
Sorry for the wait.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
How can it not be good?
It's delicious.
Yum!
Too good
This is too good!
This is not good!
This is bad!
This is good!
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I forget how to talk.
I'm going to be a mess.
We ate!
What's that so close?
Oh well...
Food report!
It's a self-medication, right?
After eating it...
It's amazing... just by putting it in my mouth...
The taste of the beef tongue, but also the saltiness that comes with it.
but the saltiness that comes with it, I thought it was wonderful.
Beef tongue goes really well with rice.
Well, I'm going to eat rice.
I mean, it's not rice, it's a snack.
Okay, I'm going to have a snack.
Here we go!
This is strawberry whip!
Banana whip
Yeah, it's good!
Well, they did something right.
Well, it turned out to be a good collaboration, didn't it?
Good job, sir.
It was insanely delicious!
Hi. Hi.
We're rehearsing for tomorrow's release event.
Thank you for watching!
yan
YANN
Ya-ya-ya!
Ya... Ya...
YAN YAN YAN YAN
Ya... Ya... Ya...
Okay then.
I'd like to do a muscle warp.
Here we go!
Let's go!
Dong-dong!
Ya!
Ya...
yan yan
Yan Yan
Don't do it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
We haven't decided where we're going to warp to.
Okay, okay
DON'T
Then...
Let's have him do a song.
Do one song.
And then we'll go on to the next one.
Now two people come out.
And then we'll talk once they come out.
I'm not talking.
Oh...
It's called "Yutan.
I had it yesterday.
It's too much!
I don't know what movie I'm watching
I'm having Jiro for lunch today.
Good evening, Mr. Renopin.
Hello. I'm Ms. Kontiklinta.
How was your first visit to Sendai?
How do you feel about the local regulations?
They're always so noisy, but now it's 10 times louder.
~~
Tickets are sold out!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
We're going to leave our mark on Sendai
We're going to leave our mark on Sendai!
We're going!
The show is about to start!
It's about to begin!
For the lies that didn't jump through the cracks
The kindness
The hate.
Cute.
Today.
I'm getting coqui'd in the park
I'm always doing this.
What's up? They took a picture of me.
Don't look.
Are you going to tie it?
It's cute.
They took a picture of me.
I'm sorry, it's a really close-up, but it only shows Yuna Yajima.
Yay!
So cute!
Okay, now I'd like to show you the girls' scene from the stage, when Chiyo Sashida and the others are all doing their thing.
Jan-cha-cha-cha, pom-pom-pom, pom-pom, pom-pom, pom-pom
Seriously, Pom-Pom Pom
I knew it
I knew it!
Yuchan, you've been so rude lately.
Excuse me for eating straight from the bowl.
Today, I was talking to Haruma...
Haruma's hair looks good.
We made fun of your no-spouse marriage, didn't we?
NG, please.
NG.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes. Yes.
Repeat after me.
Wait, wait, wait, I saw your hand.
My hand.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Look, look, look.
Director?
The irons are too loud.
Irons.
321GO.
Keep your eyes on me.
What are you doing to me?
You're so cute.
Cute lines. Cute lines.
Cute lines.
Look only at me.
What?
Too much, I'm sure it's true.
Look at me.
What?
That's the pattern.
Yi-chan, Yi-chan, say the chest-thumping line.
Chest thumping!
321.
You're the cutest!
I'm a chest-thumping girl.
Words that make you fall in love with them in 3 seconds.
321GO
Oh!
Did you call me?
I'll go anywhere you call me.
I'll go anywhere.
Thank you very much.
Really? Really?
I didn't call you.
Okay, thank you guys.
No, no, no, no, no.
321GO
Hello everyone, this is Runo Iizuka's channel.
This is Runo Iizuka's channel.
Well, the show is over now!
Now we've finished the air love high-five and we're waiting for the bonus purchase!
Oh! I've changed my make-up recently.
Oh! It's nice.
They asked me to take a picture of her eating.
He forced me to take a picture of him eating.
So cute!
Give her a compliment, Ichi-chan.
You're the cutest.
You're so cute!
You're the cutest!
I've been doing Kumon lately.
Iizuka Luna and Ichi...
Yuna said words she's never said before.
It's like they're saying things Yuna has never said.
What do you think?
Who's cuter, this grandma or Yuna?
Cute!
Cute
I've never heard it in a questioning way
I've been getting that from both of them lately.
I've been trying to cut down on the number of times I use emojis and stuff.
I'm sorry, it's okay, but stick with it.
Good morning.
Thank you very much.
Power!
I danced all the way back to Abu.
I just want to go home.
Thank you for watching!